New York State Unemployment Insurance Appeals Board Decisions 5376
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Decisions 364 69500-69999, 1959 (Box 35, Folder 9)
- Decisions 363 69000-69499, 1959 (Box 35, Folder 10)
- Decisions 373 74000-74499, 1960 (Box 36, Folder 1)
- Decisions 374 74500-74999, 1960 (Box 36, Folder 2)
- Decisions 374 75000-75499, 1960 (Box 36, Folder 3)
- Decisions 376 75500-75999, 1960 (Box 36, Folder 4)
- Decisions 377 76000-76499, 1960 (Box 36, Folder 5)
- Decisions 378 76500-76999, 1960 (Box 36, Folder 6)
- Decisions 379 77000-77499, 1960 (Box 36, Folder 7)
- Decisions 380 77500-77999, 1960 (Box 36, Folder 8)
- Decisions 381 78000-78499, 1960-1961 (Box 36, Folder 9)
- Decisions 382 78500-78999, 1961 (Box 36, Folder 10)
- Decisions 393 84000-84499, 1961 (Box 37, Folder 1)
- Decisions 394 84500-84999, 1961 (Box 37, Folder 2)
- Decisions 395 85000-85499, 1961 (Box 37, Folder 3)
- Decisions 396 85500-85999, 1961 (Box 37, Folder 4)
- Decisions 397 86000-86499, 1961 (Box 37, Folder 5)
- Decisions 398 86500-86999, 1961 (Box 37, Folder 6)
- Decisions 399 87000-87499, 1961 (Box 37, Folder 7)
- Decisions 400 87500-87999, 1961 (Box 37, Folder 8)
- Decisions 401 88000-88499, 1962 (Box 37, Folder 9)
- Decisions 402 88500-88999, 1962 (Box 37, Folder 10)
- Decisions 403 89000-89499, 1962 (Box 37, Folder 11)
- Decisions 404 90000-90499, 1962-1963 (Box 38, Folder 1)
- Decisions 405 90000-90499, 1962 (Box 38, Folder 2)
- Decisions 406 90500-90999, 1962 (Box 38, Folder 3)
- Decisions 407 91000-91499, 1962 (Box 38, Folder 4)
- Decisions 408 91500-91999, 1962-1963 (Box 38, Folder 5)
- Decisions 409 92000-92499, 1962 (Box 38, Folder 6)
- Decisions 410 92500-92999, 1962 (Box 38, Folder 7)
- Decisions 411 93000-93499, 1962 (Box 38, Folder 8)
- Decisions 413 94005-94499, 1962 (Box 38, Folder 9)
- Decisions 412 93500-94004, 1962 (Box 38, Folder 10)
- Decisions 414 94500-94999, 1962-1963 (Box 38, Folder 11)
- Decisions 415 95000-95499, 1962-1963 (Box 39, Folder 1)
- Decisions 416 95500-95999, 1962-1963 (Box 39, Folder 2)
- Decisions 417 96000-96499, 1962-1963 (Box 39, Folder 3)
- Decisions 418 96500-96999, 1963 (Box 39, Folder 4)
- Decisions 419 97000-97500, 1963 (Box 39, Folder 5)
- Decisions 420 97501-97999, 1963-1964 (Box 39, Folder 6)
- Decisions 422 88500-88999, 1963 (Box 39, Folder 7)
- Decisions 421 98000-98499, 1963-1965 (Box 39, Folder 8)
- Decisions 423 99000-99567, 1963 (Box 39, Folder 9)
- Decisions 424 99568-99999, 1963 (Box 39, Folder 10)
- Decisions 425 100000-100499, 1963 (Box 39, Folder 11)
- Decisions 426 100500-100999, 1963 (Box 40, Folder 1)
- Decisions 427 101000-101499, 1963 (Box 40, Folder 2)
- Decisions 428 101500-101999, 1963 (Box 40, Folder 3)
- Decisions 429 102000-102499, 1963 (Box 40, Folder 4)
- Decisions 430 102500-102999, 1963 (Box 40, Folder 5)
- Decisions 431 103000-103499, 1963 (Box 40, Folder 6)
- Decisions 432 103500-103999, 1963 (Box 40, Folder 7)
- Decisions 433 104000-104499, 1963 (Box 40, Folder 8)
- Decisions 434 104500-104999, 1963-1964 (Box 40, Folder 9)
- Decisions 435 105000-105499, 1963-1964 (Box 40, Folder 10)
- Decisions 436 105500-105999, 1963-1964 (Box 40, Folder 11)
- Decisions 437 106000-106499, 1963-1964 (Box 41, Folder 1)
- Decisions 438 106500-106999, 1963-1964 (Box 41, Folder 2)
- Decisions 439 107000-107499, 1963-1964 (Box 41, Folder 3)
- Decisions 440 107500-107999, 1963-1964 (Box 41, Folder 4)
- Decisions 441 108000-108499, 1964 (Box 41, Folder 5)
- Decisions 442 108500-108999, 1964 (Box 41, Folder 6)
- Decisions 443 109000-109499, 1964 (Box 41, Folder 7)
- Decisions 444 109500-109999, 1964 (Box 41, Folder 8)
- Decisions 445 110000-110499, 1964 (Box 41, Folder 9)
- Decisions 446 110500-110999, 1964 (Box 41, Folder 10)
- Decision 447 111000-111499, 1964 (Box 41, Folder 11)
- Decisions 383 79000-79499, 1961 (Box 42, Folder 1)
- Decisions 384 79500-79999, 1961 (Box 42, Folder 2)
- Decisions 385 80000-80499, 1961 (Box 42, Folder 3)
- Decisions 386 80500-80999, 1961 (Box 42, Folder 4)
- Decisions 387 81000-81499, 1961 (Box 42, Folder 5)
- Decisions 388 81500-81999, 1961 (Box 42, Folder 6)
- Decisions 389 82000-82499, 1961 (Box 42, Folder 7)
- Decisions 392 83500-83999, 1961 (Box 42, Folder 8)
- Decisions 391 83000-83499, 1961 (Box 42, Folder 9)
- Decisions 390 82500-82999, 1961 (Box 42, Folder 10)
- Decisions 448 111500-111999, 1964 (Box 43, Folder 1)
- Decisions 449 112000-112499, 1964 (Box 43, Folder 2)
- Decisions 450 112500-112999, 1964 (Box 43, Folder 3)
- Decisions 451 113000-113499, 1964 (Box 43, Folder 4)
- Decisions 452 113500-113999, 1964 (Box 43, Folder 5)
- Decisions 453 114000-114499, 1964 (Box 43, Folder 6)
- Decisions 454 114500-114999, 1964-1965 (Box 43, Folder 7)
- Decisions 455 115000-115499, 1964 (Box 43, Folder 8)
- Decisions 456 115500-115999, 1964-1965 (Box 43, Folder 9)
- Decisions 457 116000-116499, 1964-1965 (Box 43, Folder 10)
- Decisions 458 116500-116999, 1964 (Box 43, Folder 11)
- Decisions 459 117000-117499, 1964-1965 (Box 44, Folder 1)
- Decisions 470 122500-122999, 1965 (Box 45, Folder 1)
- Decisions 471 123000-123499, 1965 (Box 45, Folder 2)
- Decisions 472 123500-123999, 1965-1966 (Box 45, Folder 3)
- Decisions 473 124000-124499, 1965 (Box 45, Folder 4)
- Decisions 474 124500-124999, 1965 (Box 45, Folder 5)
- Decisions 475 125000-125499, 1965 (Box 45, Folder 6)
- Decisions 476 125500-125999, 1965 (Box 45, Folder 7)
- Decisions 477 126000-126499, 1965 (Box 45, Folder 8)
- Decisions 478 126500-126999, 1965-1966 (Box 45, Folder 9)
- Decisions 479 127000-127499, 1965-1966 (Box 45, Folder 10)
- Decisions 480 127500-127999, 1965-1966 (Box 46, Folder 1)
- Decisions 481 128000-128499, 1966 (Box 46, Folder 2)
- Decisions 482 128500-128999, 1966 (Box 46, Folder 3)
- Decisions 483 129000-129499, 1966 (Box 46, Folder 4)
- Decisions 484 129500-129999, 1966 (Box 46, Folder 5)
- Decisions 485 130000-130499, 1966 (Box 46, Folder 6)
- Decisions 486 130500-130999, 1966 (Box 46, Folder 7)
- Decisions 487 131000-131499, 1966 (Box 46, Folder 8)
- Decisions 488 131500-131999, 1966 (Box 46, Folder 9)
- Decisions 489 132000-132499, 1966 (Box 46, Folder 10)
- Decisions 490 132500-132999, 1966 (Box 47, Folder 1)
- Decisions 491 133000-133499, 1966 (Box 47, Folder 2)
- Decisions 492 133500-133999, 1966 (Box 47, Folder 3)
- Decisions 493 134000-134499, 1966 (Box 47, Folder 4)
- Decisions 494 134500-134999, 1966-1967 (Box 47, Folder 5)
- Decisions 495 135000-135499, 1966-1967 (Box 47, Folder 6)
- Decisions 496 135500-135999, 1966-1967 (Box 47, Folder 7)
- Decisions 497 136000-136499, 1967 (Box 47, Folder 8)
- Decisions 498 136500-136999, 1967 (Box 47, Folder 9)
- Decisions 499 137000-137499, 1967 (Box 47, Folder 10)
- Decisions 500 137500-137999, 1967-1968 (Box 48, Folder 1)
- Decisions 501 138000-138499, 1967 (Box 48, Folder 2)
- Decisions 502 138500-138999, 1967 (Box 48, Folder 3)
- Decisions 503 139000-139499, 1967 (Box 48, Folder 4)
- Decisions 504 139500-139999, 1967 (Box 48, Folder 5)
- Decisions 505 140000-140499, 1967 (Box 48, Folder 6)
- Decisions 506 140500-140999, 1967-1968 (Box 48, Folder 7)
- Decisions 507 141000-141499, 1967-1968 (Box 48, Folder 8)
- Decisions 508 141500-141999, 1967-1968 (Box 48, Folder 9)
- Decisions 509 142000-142499, 1967-1968 (Box 48, Folder 10)
- Decisions 510 142500-142999, 1968 (Box 49, Folder 1)
- Decisions 511 143000-143499, 1968 (Box 49, Folder 2)
- Decisions 512 143500-143999, 1968 (Box 49, Folder 3)
- Decisions 513 144000-144499, 1968 (Box 49, Folder 4)
- Decisions 514 144500-144999, 1968 (Box 49, Folder 5)
- Decisions TEC Vol. 1 1-799, 1961-1963 (Box 50, Folder 1)
- Decisions TUC Vol. 1 1-354, 1959-1961 (Box 50, Folder 2)
- Decisions TXD Vol.1 1-59, 1959-1961 (Box 50, Folder 3)
- Decisions UCFE Vol. 1 1-499, 1956-1961 (Box 50, Folder 4)
- Decisions UCFE Vol. 2 500-999, 1961-1963 (Box 50, Folder 5)
- Decisions UCFE Vol. 3 1000-1499, 1963-1964 (Box 50, Folder 6)
- Decisions UCV Vol. 1 1-149, 1954 (Box 50, Folder 7)
- Decisions UCFE Vol. 3 1000-1499, 1963-1965 (Box 50, Folder 7)
- Decisions UCV Vol.2 150-358, 1956-1960 (Box 50, Folder 8)
- MDT, TXD, TEC, etc, 1961-1970 (Box 51, Folder 1)
- UCFE 1500-1999, 1964-1967 (Box 51, Folder 2)
- UCFE 2000-2499, 1967-1971 (Box 51, Folder 3)
- Citations of Decisions Appeal Board Jan. 1, 1938 to July 1, 1947, 1938-1947 (Box 52, Folder 1)
- Appeal Board and Court Decisions Codification and Text, 1938-1939 (Box 52, Folder 2)
- Index of Appeal Board and Court Decisions, 1938-1941 (Box 52, Folder 3)
- Index of Appeal Board and Court Decisions, 1941-1942 (Box 52, Folder 4)
- Index Appeal Board and Court Decisions, 1943-1944 (Box 52, Folder 5)
- Index of Appeal Board and Court Decisions, 1945-1946 (Box 52, Folder 6)
- Index of Appeal Board and Court Decisions, 1947-1948 (Box 52, Folder 7)
- Index of Appeal Board and Court Decisions, 1949-1950 (Box 52, Folder 8)
- Index of Appeal Board and Court Decisions, 1953-1954 (Box 52, Folder 9)
- Index of Appeal Board and Court Decisions, 1951-1952 (Box 52, Folder 10)
- 61000-77999, 1963 (Box 53, Folder 1)
- 79000-79999, 1963 (Box 53, Folder 2)
- 80000-80999, 1964 (Box 53, Folder 3)
- 81000-81999, 1968 (Box 53, Folder 4)
- 82000-82999, 1963 (Box 53, Folder 5)
- 83000-83999, 1963 (Box 53, Folder 6)
- 84000-84999, 1963 (Box 53, Folder 7)
- 85000-85999, 1963 (Box 53, Folder 8)
- 86000-86999, 1963 (Box 53, Folder 9)
- 87000-87999, 1963 (Box 53, Folder 10)
- 89000-89999, 1963 (Box 53, Folder 11)
- 90000-90999, 1963 (Box 53, Folder 12)
- 91000-91999, 1964-1968 (Box 53, Folder 13)
- 92000-92999, 1976 (Box 53, Folder 14)
- 93000-93999, 1963 (Box 53, Folder 15)
- 94000-94999, 1963 (Box 53, Folder 16)
- 95000-95999, 1963 (Box 53, Folder 17)
- 96000-96999, 1963 (Box 53, Folder 18)
- 97000-97999, 1963 (Box 53, Folder 19)
- 98000-98999, 1963 (Box 53, Folder 20)
- 99000-99999, 1963 (Box 53, Folder 21)
- 100000-100999, 1963 (Box 53, Folder 22)
- 101000-101999, 1963 (Box 53, Folder 23)
- 102000-102999, 1963 (Box 53, Folder 24)
- 103000-103999, 1963 (Box 53, Folder 25)
- 104000-104999, 1963-1964 (Box 54, Folder 1)
- 105000-105999, 1963-1964 (Box 54, Folder 2)
- 106000-106999, 1963-1965 (Box 54, Folder 3)
- 107000-107999, 1964 (Box 54, Folder 4)
- 108000-108999, 1964 (Box 54, Folder 5)
- 109000-109999, 1964 (Box 54, Folder 6)
- 110000-110999, 1964 (Box 54, Folder 7)
- 111000-111999, 1964-1965 (Box 54, Folder 8)
- 115000-115999, 1964-1965 (Box 54, Folder 9)
- 116000-116999, 1964-1965 (Box 54, Folder 10)
- 112000-112999, 1964 (Box 54, Folder 11)
- 113000-113999, 1964-1965 (Box 54, Folder 12)
- 114000-114999, 1964 (Box 54, Folder 13)
- 117000-117999, 1964-1965 (Box 54, Folder 14)
- 118000-118999, 1964-1965 (Box 54, Folder 15)
- 119000-119999, 1965 (Box 55, Folder 1)
- 120000-120999, 1965 (Box 55, Folder 2)
- 121000-121999, 1965 (Box 55, Folder 3)
- 122000-122999, 1965 (Box 55, Folder 4)
- 123000-123999, 1965 (Box 55, Folder 5)
- 124000-124999, 1965 (Box 55, Folder 6)
- 125000-125999, 1965 (Box 55, Folder 7)
- 126000-126999, 1965 (Box 55, Folder 8)
- 127000-127999, 1965-1966 (Box 55, Folder 9)
- 128000-128999, 1966 (Box 55, Folder 10)
- 129000-129999, 1966 (Box 55, Folder 11)
- 130000-130999, 1966 (Box 55, Folder 12)
- 131000-133999, 1966-1967 (Box 56, Folder 1)
- 132000-132999, 1967 (Box 56, Folder 2)
- 134000-134999, 1966 (Box 56, Folder 3)
- 135000-135999, 1966-1967 (Box 56, Folder 4)
- 136000-136999, 1967 (Box 56, Folder 5)
- 137000-137999, 1967 (Box 56, Folder 6)
- 138000-138999, 1967 (Box 56, Folder 7)
- 139000-139999, 1967 (Box 56, Folder 8)
- 140000-140999, 1967-1968 (Box 56, Folder 9)
- 141000-141999, 1967-1968 (Box 56, Folder 10)
- 142000-142999, 1968 (Box 57, Folder 1)
- 143000-143999, 1968 (Box 57, Folder 2)
- 144000-144999, 1968 (Box 57, Folder 3)
- 145000-145999, 1968 (Box 57, Folder 4)
- 146000-146999, 1968 (Box 57, Folder 5)
- 147000-147999, 1968-1969 (Box 57, Folder 6)
- 148000-148999, 1968 (Box 57, Folder 7)
- 149000-149999, 1969 (Box 57, Folder 8)
- 150000-150999, 1969-1971 (Box 57, Folder 9)
- 151000-151999, 1969-1970 (Box 58, Folder 1)
- 152000-153999, 1969-1970 (Box 58, Folder 2)
- 154000-154999, 1970 (Box 58, Folder 3)
- 155000-155999, 1970 (Box 58, Folder 4)
- 156000-156999, 1970 (Box 58, Folder 5)
- 157000-157999, 1970-1971 (Box 58, Folder 6)
- 158000-158999, 1970-1971 (Box 58, Folder 7)
- 159000-159999, 1970-1971 (Box 58, Folder 8)
- 160000-160999, 1970-1971 (Box 58, Folder 9)
- 161000-161999, 1971 (Box 58, Folder 10)
- 162000-162999, 1971 (Box 58, Folder 11)
- 163000-163999, 1971 (Box 58, Folder 12)
- 164000-164999, 1971 (Box 58, Folder 13)
- 165000-165999, 1971-1972 (Box 58, Folder 14)
- 167000-167985A, 1971-1975 (Box 58, Folder 15)
- 166000-166999, 1971 (Box 58, Folder 16)
- Misc., 1964-1970 (Box 58, Folder 17)
- 168000-168999, 1972 (Box 59, Folder 1)
- 169000-169999, 1972 (Box 59, Folder 2)
- 170000-170999, 1972 (Box 59, Folder 3)
- 171000-171999, 1972 (Box 59, Folder 4)
- 172000-172999, 1972 (Box 59, Folder 5)
- 173000-173999, 1972 (Box 59, Folder 6)
- 174000-174999, 1972 (Box 59, Folder 7)
- 175000-175999, 1972-1975 (Box 59, Folder 8)
- 176000-176999, 1972-1973 (Box 59, Folder 9)
- 177000-177999, 1972-1973 (Box 59, Folder 10)
- 178000-178999, 1972-1973 (Box 59, Folder 11)
- 179000-179999, 1973 (Box 59, Folder 12)
- 180000-180999, 1973 (Box 59, Folder 13)
- 181000-181999, 1973-1974 (Box 59, Folder 14)
- 182000-182999, 1972-1974 (Box 59, Folder 15)
- 183000-183999, 1973 (Box 59, Folder 16)
- 184000-184999, 1973-1974 (Box 59, Folder 17)
- 186000-186999, 1973-1974 (Box 60, Folder 1)
- 187000-187999, 1973-1974 (Box 60, Folder 2)
- 188000-188999, 1974-1975 (Box 60, Folder 3)
- 189000-189999, 1972-1976 (Box 60, Folder 4)
- 190000-190999, 1974-1975 (Box 60, Folder 5)
- 191000-191999, 1974 (Box 60, Folder 6)
- 185000-185999, 1973-1975 (Box 60, Folder 7)
- 192000-192999, 1974 (Box 60, Folder 8)
- 193000-193999, 1974 (Box 60, Folder 9)
- 194000-194999, 1974-1975 (Box 60, Folder 10)
- 195000-195999, 1974-1975 (Box 60, Folder 11)
- 196000-196999, 1974-1975 (Box 60, Folder 12)
- 197000-197999, 1974-1976 (Box 60, Folder 13)
- 198000-198999, 1974-1975 (Box 60, Folder 14)
- 199000-199999, 1974-1975 (Box 60, Folder 15)
- 200000-200999, 1974-1975 (Box 60, Folder 16)
- 201000-201999, 1975-1976 (Box 60, Folder 17)
- 202000-202999, 1975 (Box 60, Folder 18)
- 203000-203999, 1975 (Box 60, Folder 19)
- 204000-204999, 1975 (Box 60, Folder 20)
- 205000-205999, 1975 (Box 60, Folder 21)
- 206000-206999, 1975 (Box 60, Folder 22)
- 207000-207999, 1975-1976 (Box 60, Folder 23)
- 208000-208999, 1975 (Box 60, Folder 24)
- 209000-209999, 1975 (Box 60, Folder 25)
- 210000-210999, 1975-1976 (Box 60, Folder 26)
- 211000-211999, 1975 (Box 61, Folder 1)
- 212000-212999, 1975-1976 (Box 61, Folder 2)
- 213000-213999, 1975-1976 (Box 61, Folder 3)
- 214000-214999, 1975-1976 (Box 61, Folder 4)
- 215000-215999, 1975-1976 (Box 61, Folder 5)
- 216000-216999, 1975-1976 (Box 61, Folder 6)
- 217000-217999, 1976 (Box 61, Folder 7)
- 218000-218999, 1976 (Box 61, Folder 8)
- 219000-219999, 1976 (Box 61, Folder 9)
- 220000-220999, 1976 (Box 61, Folder 10)
- 221000-221999, 1976 (Box 61, Folder 11)
- 222000-222999, 1976 (Box 61, Folder 12)
- 223000-223999, 1976 (Box 61, Folder 13)
- 224000-224999, 1976 (Box 61, Folder 14)
- 225000-225999, 1976 (Box 61, Folder 15)
- 226000-226999, 1976 (Box 61, Folder 16)
- 227000-227999, 1976 (Box 61, Folder 17)
- 228000-228999, 1976-1977 (Box 61, Folder 18)
- 229000-229999, 1976 (Box 61, Folder 19)
- 229000-229999, 1975-1976 (Box 61, Folder 20)
- 231000-231999, 1976 (Box 62, Folder 1)
- 232000-232999, 1976-1977 (Box 62, Folder 2)
- 233000-233999, 1976-1977 (Box 62, Folder 3)
- 234000-234999, 1976-1977 (Box 62, Folder 4)
- 235000-235999, 1977 (Box 62, Folder 5)
- 236000-236999, 1977 (Box 62, Folder 6)
- 237000-237999, 1977 (Box 62, Folder 7)
- 238000-238999, 1977 (Box 62, Folder 8)
- 239000-239999, 1977 (Box 62, Folder 9)
- 240000-240999, 1977-1979 (Box 62, Folder 10)
- 241000-241999, 1977 (Box 62, Folder 11)
- 242000-242999, 1977 (Box 62, Folder 12)
- 243000-243999, 1977 (Box 62, Folder 13)
- 244000-244999, 1977 (Box 62, Folder 14)
- 245000-245999, 1977 (Box 62, Folder 15)
- 246000-246999, 1977-1978 (Box 62, Folder 16)
- 247000-247999, 1977 (Box 62, Folder 17)
- 248000-248999, 1977 (Box 62, Folder 18)
- 249000-249999, 1977 (Box 62, Folder 19)
- 250000-250999, 1977-1978 (Box 63, Folder 1)
- 251000-251999, 1977-1978 (Box 63, Folder 2)
- 252000-252999, 1977 (Box 63, Folder 3)
- 253000-253999, 1977-1978 (Box 63, Folder 4)
- 254000-254999, 1977-1978 (Box 63, Folder 5)
- 255000-255999, 1977 (Box 63, Folder 6)
- 256000-256999, 1977-1978 (Box 63, Folder 7)
- 257000-257999, 1977-1978 (Box 63, Folder 8)
- 258000-258999, 1977-1978 (Box 63, Folder 9)
- 259000-259999, 1977-1978 (Box 63, Folder 10)
- 260000-260999, 1978 (Box 63, Folder 11)
- 261000-261999, 1978 (Box 63, Folder 12)
- 262000-262999, 1978 (Box 63, Folder 13)
- 263000-263999, 1978 (Box 63, Folder 14)
- 264000-264999, 1978 (Box 63, Folder 15)
- 265000-265999, 1978 (Box 63, Folder 16)